Guide to the Women's International League for Peace and Freedom Collection ARS.0056
Archive of Recorded Sound
- 3. Palo Alto Branch., 1979 -1986
  - 4. Elizabeth Drake Interview., 1982-11-09 to 1982-11-23; Drake, Elizabeth; Madrid, Rosanna
    - Transcript; Rough Transcript edited by Elizabeth Drake; Bio/historical note; Index; Interview Notes, November 10, 1982; Letter to Senator Alan Cranston; Oral History Report on Interview by Rosanna Maria Madrid., 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - 5. Barbara Gado Interview., 1981-01-31 and 1981-02-18; Buffington, Lana; Gado, Barbara
    - Interview, January 30, 1981, and February 12, 1981., 1981-01-30 and 1981-02-12; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 241)
    - Interview, February 18, 1981., 1981-02-18; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 242)
    - Transcript; Bio/historical note; Index and table of contents for interview; interview excerpts., 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - 6. Fran Gillis Interview., 1984-05-17; Gillis, Fran; Ruben, Lisa
    - Interview, May 17, 1984, Part One., 1984-05-17; 1 audiocassette (Audio 3, Cassette 101)
    - Interview, May 17, 1984, Part Two., 1984-05-17; 1 audiocassette (Audio 3, Cassette 102)
    - Bio/historical note; Index., 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - 7. Leah Halper Interview., 1984-06-01 and 1984-11-09; Halper, Leah; Jacobs, Margaret; Rodriguez, Theresa
    - Interview, June 1, 1984., 1984-06-01; 1 audiocassette (Audio 3, Cassette 103)
    - Interview, November 9, 1984., 1984-11-09; 1 audiocassette (Audio 3, Cassette 104)
  - 8. Helen Hildreth Interview., 1981-01-30 and 1981-02-18; Hildreth, Helen; Vargas, Iola
    - Interview, January 30, 1981, Part One., 1981-01-30; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 236)
    - Interview, January 30, 1981, Part Two, and February 18, 1981, Part One., 1981-01-30 and 1981-02-18; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 237)
    - Interview, February 18, 1981, Part Two., 1981-02-18; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 238)
    - Transcript; Bio/historical note; Index; Iola Wescott's Oral History Report on the Interview, February, 26, 1981; Newspaper clipping, February 27, 1950., 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - 9. Doris Cohen Jones Interview., 1981-02-03 to 1981-02-26; Glover, Babs; Jones, Doris Cohen
    - Interview, February 3, 1981, February 20, 1981, and February 24, 1981, Part One., 1981-02-03 to 1981-02-24; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 234)
      A transcribed excerpt from this interview can be found in, Adams, Judith Porter. (1991). Peacework: Oral Histories of Women Peace Activists. Boston: Twayne Publishers"
    - Interview, February 24, 1981, Part Two, and February 26, 1981, Part One., 1981-02-24 to 1981-02-26; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 235)
    - Interview, February 26, 1981, Part Two., 1981-02-26; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 236)
    - Bio/historical note; Index; Letter to Judy Adams, January 12, 1985; Student paper by Babs Glover; Newpaper clippings; Other papers., 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - 10. Audrey Keller Interview., 1989-04-29; Adams, Judith Porter; Keller, Audrey
    - Interview, April 29, 1989, Part One., 1989-04-29; 1 audiocassette (Audio 3, Cassette 105)
    - Interview, April 29, 1989, Part Two., 1989-04-29; 1 audiocassette (Audio 3, Cassette 106)
    - Bio/historical note; Transcript; Rough Transcripts edited by Audrey Keller; Newspaper article from Los Angeles Times, July 31, 1985., 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 8.1)
  - 11. Martina Korver Interview., 1982; Hancock, Elizabeth; Korver, Martina
    - Interview, Spring 1982., 1 audiocassette (Audio 3, Cassette 107)
    - Interview, Spring 1982, copy one., 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 242)
    - Interview, Spring 1982, copy two., 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 243)
    - Bio/historical note; Index., 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 12. Millee Livingstone Interview., 1980-06-03; Geyer, Alyssa; Livingstone, Millee
    - Interview, June 3, 1980., 1980-06-03; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 236)
    - Bio/historical note; Index., 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 13. Olive Mayer Interview., 1986-07-24 to 1986-12-05; Ludwig, Margie; Mayer, Olive
    - Interview, July 24, 1986., 1986-07-24; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 108)
    - Interview, August 5, 1986, Part One., 1986-08-05; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 109)
    - Interview, August 5, 1986, Part Two., 1986-08-05; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 110)
    - Interview, October 10, 1986 and October 15, 1986, Part One., 1986-10-10 and 1986-10-15; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 111)
    - Interview, October 15, 1986, Part Two., 1986-10-15; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 112)
    - Interview, October 15, 1986, Part Three., 1986-10-15; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 113)
    - Interview, December 5, 1986, Part One., 1986-12-05; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 114)
    - Interview, December 5, 1986, Part Two., 1986-12-05; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 115)
    - Interview, December 5, 1986, Part Three., 1986-12-05; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 116)
    - Bio/historical note; Index; Transcripts., 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - 14. Elizabeth Mitchell Interview., 1982-05-04 to 1985-07-20; Burgard, Renee; Jurin-Reid, Barbara; Mitchell, Elizabeth
    - Interview, May 4, 1982, Part One., 1982-05-04; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 117)
    - Interview, May 4, 1982, Part Two., 1982-05-04; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 118)
    - Interview, May 4, 1982, copy., 1982-05-04; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 254)
    - Interview, May 11, 1982, Part One., 1982-05-11; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 119)
    - Interview, May 11, 1982, Part Two., 1982-05-11; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 120)
    - Interview, May 11, 1982, copy., 1982-05-11; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 255)
    - Interview, July 20, 1985., 1985-07-20; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 121)
    - Bio/historical note; Index; History of Interviews by Barbara Jurin-Reid; Notes on the Interviews; Other Papers., 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - 15. Esther Newill Interview., 1980-02-20 to 1980-02-23; Newill, Esther; Shaw, Linda
    - Interview, February 20, 1980 and February 23, 1980, Part One., 1980-02-20 to 1980-02-23; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 248)
    - Interview, February 23, 1980, Part Two., 1981-02-23; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 249)
    - Bio/historical note; Index; Newspaper Clippings., 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - 16. Linus Pauling Interview., 1986-01-28; Adams, Judith Porter; Burgard, Renee; Pauling, Linus, 1901-1994
    Scope and contents
    Linus Pauling discussing the peace work of his wife, Ava Helen Pauling
    Pauling, Ava Helen
    - Interview, January 28, 1986, Part One., 1986-01-28; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 124)
    - Interview, January 28, 1986, Part Two., 1986-01-28; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 125)
    - Transcript; Newspaper Clipping, November 2, 1981; Newspaper Clipping, November 8, 1979; Newpaper Clipping, December 8, 1981; Obituary; Letter to Alice Richards, September 21, 1964; Essay on Bertha von Suttner by Ava Pauling; Other Papers., 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - 17. Stella Polya Interview., 1981-02-08 and 1981-03-08; Levenson, Amy; Polya, Stella
    - Interview, February 8, 1981 and March 8, 1981., 1981-02-08 and 1981-03-08; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 233)
    - Bio/historical note; Index; Newspaper clippings; History of the Interviews., 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - 18. Elsie Renne Interview., 1981-02-27 to 1981-03-13; Maillard, Paige; Renne, Elsie
    - Interview, February 27, 1981., 1981-02-27; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 239)
    - Interview, March 11, 1981, and March 13, 1981., 1981-03-11 and 1981-03-13; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 240)
    - Bio/historical note; Index; Newspaper clippings., 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - 19. Alice Richards Interview., 1981-02-02 to 1981-03-16; Adams, Judith Porter; Puerta, Rosemarie; Richards, Alice
    - Interview, February 2, 1981, February 9, 1981, and February 23, 1981., 1981-02-02 to 1981-02-23; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 249)
    - Interview, March 16, 1981., 1981-03-16; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 250)
    - Transcript; Letters to Judy Adams; Bio/historical note; Index; Funeral service program, June 20, 2011; Letter to Alice Richards' Mother, March 19, 1935; Other Papers., 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Retrospective: Alice Schott Richards., circa 2005; 1 folder; Halper, Leah (Box 13)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - 20. Pauline Scott Interview., 1984-02-17 to 1984-10-05; Halper, Leah; Scott, Pauline
    - Interview, February 17, 1984., 1984-02-17; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 126)
    - Interview, September 24, 1984, Part One., 1984-09-24; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 127)
    - Interview, September 24, 1984, Part Two., 1984-09-24; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 128)
    - Interview, September 28, 1984, Part One., 1984-09-28; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 129)
    - Interview, September 28, 1984, Part Two., 1984-09-28; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 130)
    - Interview, October 5, 1984., 1984-10-05; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 131)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - 21. Mary Shepardson Interview., 1982-04-20 to 1982-05-07; Fair, Mary; Shepardson, Mary
    - Interview, April 20, 1982., 1982-04-20; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 132)
    - Interview, April 20, 1982, copy., 1982-04-20; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 251)
    - Interview, May 7, 1982., 1982-05-07; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 133)
    - Interview, May 7, 1982, copy., 1982-05-07; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 250)
    - Bio/historical note; Other papers., 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - 22. Ann Sims Interview., 1982-05-10 to 1982-05-27; Shaw, Linda; Sims, Ann; Sims, Lyn
    - Interview, May 10, 1982, Part One., 1982-05-10; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 134)
    - Interview, May 10, 1982, Part Two., 1982-05-10; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 135)
    - Interview, May 27, 1982., 1982-05-27; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 136)
      Interview with both Sims and her daughter Lyn.
    - Thorstein Veblen (Sims' father) Bio/historical note., 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - 23. Fiona St. John Interview., 1986-04-13 to 1986-06-02; Jacobs, Margaret; St. John, Fiona
    - Interview, April 13, 1986., 1986-04-13; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 137)
    - Interview, May 2, 1986 and June 2, 1986., 1986-05-02 and 1986-06-02; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 138)
    - Bio/historical note., 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - 24. Margaret Stein Interview., 1986-11-18 to 1986-12-7; Breckenridge, Emily; Stein, Margaret
    - Interview, November 18, 1986., 1986-11-18; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 139)
    - Interview, November 22, 1986., 1986-11-22; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 140)
    - Interview, December 4, 1986, Part One., 1986-12-04; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 141)
    - Interview, December 4, 1986, Part Two., 1986-12-04; 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 142)
    - Interview, December 7, 1986., 1986-12-07; 1 audiocassette 1 audiocassette (Audio 4, Cassette 143)
    - Bio/historical note; Index; Transcript; Interview excerpts; Interviewer notes., 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - 25. Henrietta Troyan Interview., 1982 to 1984-11-08; Hancock, Elizabeth; Jacobs, Margaret; Troyan, Henrietta
    - Interview, Spring 1982., 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 144)
    - Interview, November 18, 1984., 1984-11-18; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 145)
    - Obituary; Bio/historical note; Index; Transcript., 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 26. Marion Wachtel Interview., 1981-01-26 to 1981-02-27; Thomas, Sally; Wachtel, Marion
    - Interview, January 26, 1981., 1981-01-26; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 146)
    - Interview, January, 26, 1981 and February 2, 1981, copy., 1981-01-26 to 1981-02-02; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 245)
    - Interview, February 2, 1981., 1981-02-02; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 147)
    - Interview, February 14, 1981, Part One., 1981-02-14; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 148)
    - Interview, February 14, 1981, Part Two and February 27, 1981 Part One., 1981-02-14 and 1981-02-27; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 149)
    - Interview, February 27, 1981, Part Two., 1981-02-27; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 150)
    - Interview, February 14, 1981 and February 27, 1981 Part One, copy., 1981-02-14 and 1981-02-27; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 246)
    - Interview, February 27, 1981, copy., 1981-02-27; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 247)
    - Bio/historical note; Index; Oral history report by Lucy Ostrander; Newspaper clipping, April 27, 1986; Newspaper clipping, September 15, 1983; Newspaper clipping, April 21, 1982; Obituary., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - 27. Louise Wilson Interview., 1984-07-04 to 1984-10-22; Halper, Leah; Wilson, Louise
    - Interview, July 4, 1984, Part One., 1984-07-04; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 151)
    - Interview, July 4, 1984, Part Two and July 27, 1984, Part One., 1984-07-04 and 1984-07-27; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 152)
    - Interview, July 27, 1984, Part Two., 1984-07-27; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 153)
    - Interview, August 15, 1984., 1984-08-15; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 154)
    - Interview, October 10, 1984, Part One., 1984-10-10; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 155)
    - Interview, October 10, 1984, Part Two., 1984-10-10; 1 audiocassette (Cassette 5, Cassette 156)
    - Interview, October 22, 1984., 1984-10-22; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 157)
    - Bio/historical note; Index; Obituary., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 58)
- 4. Santa Cruz Branch., 1981-1986
  - 1. Mary B. Duffield Interview., 1986-03-01; Coe, Liz; Duffield, Mary B.
    - Interview, March 1, 1986, Part One., 1986-03-01; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 158)
    - Interview, March 1, 1986, Part Two., 1986-03-01; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 159)
    - Letter to Judy Adams, April 16, 1989; Bio/historical note; Redwood Youth Foundation Brochure; Newspaper clipping, May 1984; Magazine clipping, January, 1965; Earle L. Reynolds bio; Other newspaper clippings, papers., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - 2. Ellie Foster Interview., 1985-12-06 and 1985-12-14; Coe, Liz; Foster, Ellie
    - Interview, December 6, 1985., 1985-12-06; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 160)
    - Interview, December 14, 1985., 1985-12-14; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 161)
    - Funeral service program., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - 3. Lucy Haessler Interview., 1981-04-29 to 1982-06-03; Haessler, Lucy; Robnett, Cary Susan
    - Interview, April 29, 1981., 1981-04-29; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 162)
    - Interview, May 18, 1981, Part One., 1981-05-18; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 163)
    - Interview, April 29, 1981 and May 18, 1981, Part One, copy., 1981-04-29 and 1981-05-18; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 8, Reel 256)
    - Interview, May 18, 1981, Part Two., 1981-05-18; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 164)
    - Interview, June 3, 1982., 1982-06-03; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 165)
    - Interview, May 18, 1981, Part Two, and June 3, 1982, copy., 1981-05-18 and 1982-06-03; 1 7" open reel tape(s) (Audio 6, Reel 257)
    - Bio/historical note; Index; Newspaper clipping, August 26, 1980; Newspaper clipping, August 27, 1975; Newspaper clipping, May 31, 1979; Newspaper clipping, August 26, 1980; Congressional Record, April 11, 1984; Letter from Congressman Geo W. Crockett, Jr., April 6, 1984; Other papers., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 18)
- 5. Branches Outside California., 1986-1989
  - 1. Charlotte Adams Interview., 1988-01-23; Adams, Charlotte, 1903? - 2005; Gamble, Dee
    - Interview, January 23, 1988., 1988-01-23; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 166)
    - Transcript; Bio/historical note; Newspaper clipping, November 12, 1987., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - 2. Donna Allen Interview., 1989-04-26; Allen, Donna, 1920-1999; Drake, Joan
    - Interview, April 26, 1989, Part One., 1989-04-26; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 167)
    - Interview, April 26, 1989, Part Two., 1989-04-26; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 168)
    - Transcript; Bio/historical notes; Obituaries., 1 folder; Allen, Donna, 1920-1999; Drake, Joan (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - 3. Elise Boulding Interview., 1988-02-08; Boulding, Elise; Gore, Jean
    - Interview, February 8, 1988, Part One., 1988-02-08; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 169)
    - Interview, February 8, 1988, Part Two., 1988-02-08; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 170)
    - Bio/historical note., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 4. Emily Lucile Burns Interview., 1988-01-19; Burns, Emily Lucile; Paisley, John; Paisley, Miriam
    - Interview, January 19, 1988, Part One., 1988-01-19; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 171)
    - Interview, January 19, 1988, Part Two., 1988-01-19; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 172)
    - Bio/historical note; Transcript., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 5. Mary Bess Cameron Interview., 1987-05-05; Cameron, Mary Bess; Parnes, Brenda
    - Bio/historical note; Transcript., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 6. Kay Camp Interview., 1987-09-24 and 1987-10-02; Adams, Judith Porter; Camp, Kay
    - Interview, September 24, 1987, Part One., 1987-09-24; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 173)
    - Interview, September 24, 1987, Part Two., 1987-09-24; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 174)
    - Interview, October 2, 1987., 1987-10-02; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 175)
    - Transcript; Background information; Obituaries., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - 7. Kay Cole Interview., 1986-03-01 to 1986-03-31; Cole, Kay; Wilson, Beth
    - Interview, March 1, 1986., 1986-03-01; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 176)
    - Interview, March 10, 1986., 1986-03-10; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 177)
    - Interview, March 31, 1986., 1986-03-31; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 178)
    - Transcript; Obituary., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - 8. Miriam Cornelius Interview., 1989-08-07; Cornelius, Miriam; Paisley, John; Paisley, Miriam
    - Interview, August 7, 1989., 1989-08-07; 1 audiocassette (Audio 5, Cassette 179)
    - Transcript., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 9. Virginia Durr Interview., 1989-02-22; Adams, Judith Porter; Durr, Virginia Foster
    - Interview, February 22, 1989., 1989-02-22; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 180)
    - Bio/historical note; Obituary., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - 10. Margaret Gilstrop Interview., 1987-09-30; Adams, Judith Porter; Gilstrop, Margaret
    - Interview, September 30, 1987, Part One., 1987-09-30; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 181)
    - Interview, September 30, 1987, Part Two., 1987-09-30; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 182)
  - 11. Marii Hasegawa Interview., 1987; Adams, Judith Porter; Hasegawa, Marii
    - Interview, October 1987, Part One., 1987-10; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 183)
    - Interview, October 1987, Part Two., 1987-10; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 184)
    - Bio/historical note., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - 12. Minnie Belle Hoch Interview., 1988-01-13; Hoch, Minne Belle; Paisley, John; Paisley, Miriam
    - Interview, January 13, 1988., 1988-01-13; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 185)
    - Transcript., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - 13. Sadie Hughley Interview., 1988-02-17; Gamble, Dee; Hughley, Sadie
    - Interview, February 17, 1988., 1988-02-17; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 186)
    - Copy of memorial service booklet; Information on TV documentary "The Durrs of Montgomery"; Other papers., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - 14. Rozi Kuerti Interview., 1988-11-19; Kuerti, Rozi; Rivers, Ann
    - Interview, November 19, 1988., 1988-11-19; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 187)
    - Bio/historical note; Transcript., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - 15. Amy Kurkjian Interview., 1987-10-03; Adams, Judith Porter; Kurkjian, Amy
    - Transcript., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - 16. Mary McCorkle Interview., 1987-10-03; Adams, Judith Porter; McCorkle, Mary
    - Interview, October 3, 1987, Part One., 1987-10-03; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 188)
    - Interview, October 3, 1987, Part Two., 1987-10-03; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 189)
    - Interview, October 3, 1987, Part Three., 1987-10-03; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 190)
    - Index., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - 17. Mary McWhorter Interview., 1987-09-28; Adams, Judith Porter; McWhorter, Mary
    - Interview, September 28,1987, Part One., 1987-09-28; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 191)
    - Interview, September 28, 1987, Part Two., 1987-09-28; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 192)
    - Interview, September 28, 1987, Part Three., 1987-09-28; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 193)
    - Index., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - 18. Mariagnes Medrud Interview., 1988-02-12 to 1988-02-22; Gore, Jean; Medrud, Mariagnes
    - Interview, February 12, 1988., 1988-02-12; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 194)
    - Interview, February 17, 1988., 1988-02-17; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 195)
    - Interview, February 22, 1988, Part One., 1988-02-22; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 196)
    - Interview, February 22, 1988, Part Two., 1988-02-22; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 197)
    - Bio/historical note., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - 19. Janet Neuman Interview., 1987-10-02; Adams, Judith Porter; Neuman, Janet N.
    - Interview, October 2, 1987, Part One., 1987-10-02; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 198)
    - Interview, October 2, 1987, Part Two., 1987-10-02; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 199)
    - Poems by Janet Neuman., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - 20. Adelaide Noyes Interview., 1988-01-12; Noyes, Adelaide; Paisley, Miriam
    - Bio/historical note; Transcript., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - 21. Ruth Pinkson Interview., 1987-10; Adams, Judith Porter; Pinkson, Ruth
    - Interview, October 1987, Part One., 1987-10; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 200)
    - Interview, October 1987, Part Two., 1987-10; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 201)
    - Bio/historical note., 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Photographs., 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - 22. Louise Robison Interview., 1988-11-09 and 1988-12-14; Pederson, Sharon; Robison, Louise
    - Interview, November 9, 1988., 1988-11-09; 1 audiocassette (Audio 6, Cassette 202)